[
  {
    "question": "what is flutter",
    "answer": "Flutter transforms the entire app development process. Frontend and full-stack developers use Flutter to build an application\u2019s user interface (UI) for multiple platforms. Flutter is often used with DART, which is an object-oriented programming language by Google."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is flutter",
    "answer": "Flutter transforms the entire app development process. Frontend and full-stack developers use Flutter to build an application\u2019s user interface (UI) for multiple platforms. Flutter is often used with DART, which is an object-oriented programming language by Google."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is python",
    "answer": "Python is an interpreted, object-oriented, high-level programming language with dynamic semantics. Python consistently ranks as one of the most popular programming languages. It's designed to be used in a range of applications, including data science, software and web development, automation, and generally getting stuff done."
  },
  {
    "question": "who is the prime minister of bangladesh",
    "answer": "The current prime minister is Sheikh Hasina, appointed on 6 January 2009 by president Iajuddin Ahmed. She is the longest serving prime minister in the country's history. She assumed the office on 12 January 2014 for the third time after her party Awami League-led grand alliance won the January 5 Parliamentary elections."
  },
  {
    "question": "about Hajrat Muhammad",
    "answer": "According to Islamic doctrine, he was a prophet divinely inspired to preach and confirm the monotheistic teachings of Adam, Abraham, Moses, Jesus, and other prophets. He is believed to be the Seal of the Prophets within Islam, with the Quran as well as his. . ."
  },
  {
    "question": "about Allah",
    "answer": "Allah is the common Arabic word for God. In the English language, the word generally refers to God in Islam. The name Allah is probably a contraction of the Arabic al-Ilah, 'the God,' and its origins can be traced to the earliest Semitic writings, in which the word for god was il, el, or eloah."
  },
  {
    "question": "about Scikit-learn",
    "answer": "This project was started in 2007 as a Google Summer of Code project by David Cournapeau. The name of the project stems from the notion that it is a \"SciKit\" (SciPy Toolkit), a separately developed and distributed third-party extension to SciPy."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is body mass index",
    "answer": "Body Mass Index (BMI) is a person's weight in kilograms (or pounds) divided by the square of height in meters (or feet) A high BMI can indicate high body fatness. BMI screens for weight categories that may lead to health problems, but it does not diagnose the health of an individual."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is about RAM",
    "answer": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory, and if you've ever opened a lap- or desktop computer, you've seen it. it's the temporary storage in your computer that gives applications a place to store and access data on a short-term basis. a computer that temporarily stores data can be accessed and read almost instantly."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is about Motion",
    "answer": "physics is a physics that studies how things move. motion changes the orientation of a body. motion changes the orientation of a body."
  }
]